drupalgardens.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy | Drupal Gardens

Acquia, Inc (“Acquia”) operates the Drupal Gardens website (the “Service”). It is Acquia’s policy to respect the privacy of both people who create websites on the Service (“Customers”) as well as people who become users of those sites (“Users”).

Your privacy is important to us. The Drupal Gardens privacy policy is designed around these principals:

  * We don’t ask for your personal information unless we truly need it
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, for product development purposes, or to protect our rights
  * We don’t market to the Users of your website unless they are also a Customer of Acquia

**Gathering of Non-Personally Identifying Information**

Acquia collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Acquia’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Acquia’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Acquia may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. Acquia also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Acquia does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Drupal Gardens website (DrupalGardens.com), and to websites built on Drupal Gardens, choose to interact with the sites in ways that require Acquia to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Acquia gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website on Drupal Gardens to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Acquia, for example by purchasing a subscription to Drupal Gardens, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Acquia collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Acquia. Acquia does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information**

Acquia takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personally identifying information. Acquia discloses personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Acquia’s behalf or to provide services available at Acquia’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Acquia’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Acquia will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Acquia discloses personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Acquia believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Acquia, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Acquia website and have supplied your email address, Acquia may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Acquia and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a unique text file that a web site can send to your browser software. Cookies enable a web site to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. Acquia uses cookies to help Acquia identify and track visitors, their usage of Acquia website, and their website access preferences. If you do not want Acquia to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Note that certain features of Acquia’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

We do not provide any personally identifiable Customer or User information to advertisers or to third-party Web sites. Ads appearing on any of the websites on the Service may be delivered by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Acquia and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Acquia encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@acquia.com](mailto:legal@acquia.com).

Some of the terms in this privacy policy were borrowed from [Automattic.com](http://automattic.com/privacy/), who was gracious enough to make their privacy policy available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.

Last update: 2010-01-25
